smarttuition.com 2013-09-30

# Privacy | Smart Tuition - Tuition Management For K-12 Catholic Schools, Private Schools, Christian Schools, Independent Schools, Jewish Schools, Boarding Schools

##### Privacy & Security

Protecting the privacy of our clients’ personal and financial information is our highest priority. The informatoin listed below explains how Smart Tuition protects your information. If there are any questions that this statement does not address, please contact us. 

##### Confidentiality

Smart Tuition has adopted numerous procedures to protect the confidentiality of you and your school’s information. Smart Tuition’s service representatives are instructed to provide information to, and accept instructions from only the parent(s) or guardian(s) named on the account as well as school employees who have been specifically authorized in writing to work with Smart Tuition. All of the information that we maintain on your accounts is filed in a secure location, and all trash is shredded. We do not disclose any nonpublic personal information about our customers or former customers to anyone, except as permitted by law.

##### Privacy Policy

We take privacy seriously and we value yours. We do not disclose any nonpublic personal information about our customers or former customers to anyone except as permitted by law. Smart tuition has adopted numerous procedures to protect the confidentiality of school and family information. We may collect personally identifiable information when you visit our site through the use of cookies. We also receive and record information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookie information and the page(s) you have visited.

##### Security Policy

Access to your personal and account information is restricted to those employees who need to know that information as part of their job, to service your account or to provide products and services to you. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that are designed to guard your nonpublic personal information. We adhere to the Payment Security Industries Standard for storing card holder data.
